

# Sanghyun Park

AUTONOMOUS DRIVING SYSTEM · SLAM · PERCEPTION

37, Kyungsoo-daero 610-gil, Dong an-gu, Anyang-si, Gyunggi-do, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-2387-4617 | ■ pash0302@naver.com | ★ SanghyunPark01.github.io | □ SanghyunPark01

"Can't get anything without trying"

# Summary.

This is Sanghyun Park, who wants to become a 0.1% of Robotics engineer. I'm interested in Autonomous driving system of mobile robot and vehicle, SLAM and Sensor Fusion. I think the more research on these technologies develops, the more convenient human life becomes. Therefore, I would like to contribute to this research.

## Research Interests

**Robotics** Visual SLAM, Mobile Robot, Sensor Fusion, Dynamic Object Detection

# Education \_\_\_\_\_

## **KwangWoon University**

**B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS** 

Current GPA: 4.18/4.5, Current Major GPA: 4.25/4.5
 Club: Baram (Robotics Academic Group) - [2022 Staff]

Seoul, S.Korea

Mar. 2020 - Feb. 2024(Expected)

# Work Experience

#### **Urban Robotics LAB @KAIST**

UNDERGRADUATE LAB INTERN (ADVISOR: PROF.HYUN MYUNG)

• Research on Multi-Sensor Fusion SLAM for Mobinn Mobile Robot

# Robotics & A.I. LAB @KwangWoon University

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor : Prof.Junghyun Oh)

- Research on Visual SLAM and Computer Vision
- Studying Visual SLAM in Dynamic Environment

#### Daejeon, S.Korea

July. 2023 - Present

# Seoul, S.Korea

December. 2021 - August. 2022

## Honors & Awards

## Honors

2020-2	Academic Scholarship, One-quarter tuition	KwangWoon Univ.
2021-1	Academic Scholarship, One-quarter tuition	KwangWoon Univ.
2022-1	Academic Scholarship, One-quarter tuition	KwangWoon Univ.
2022-2	Academic Scholarship, One-quarter tuition	KwangWoon Univ.

#### **AWARDS**

2023-1 Encouragement award, SHARE robot contest

Shared Al-Robotics
Education School

# Skills\_\_\_

Programming C++/C, Python, Matlab
DevOps ROS, Git, Docker
Frameworks Pytorch, Tensorflow

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

#### **QS Bot - Quarantine & Security Bot**

Baram(Robotics Academic Group)

Mobile Robot, Moving Object Detection, Charging Station Docking System, SLAM, Navigation, Motor Control

September.2022 - January.2023

- This project is a Team Project
- I worked on Moving Object Detection and Charging Station Docking System
- This project is in my Github repository: QS Bot [Link]

#### **NRGAN: Neural Radiance GAN Network for Photorealistic Space Design**

Capston Design March.2023 - June.2023

NERF, CYCLEGAN

- This project propose a method of neural radiance GAN to enable photorealistic design
- Our model combines NeRF and CycleGAN

## an model compiled text and by steel in

VISUAL ODOMETRY, IMAGE PREPROCESSING, PYTHON

**Visual Odometry with image preprocessing** 

3D Objection Detection(LiDAR) & Camera Align

Robotics & A.I. LAB (KW Univ.) February.2022 - February.2022

Limplemented visual odometry based on ORB features using Python

• Visual Odometry is improved in terms of path accuracy when applying Gaussian filter using OpenCV: Result[Link]

Baram(Robotics Academic Group)

March.2022 - July.2022

OPENPCDET, NUMPY, ROS

- Lused PointRCNN pretrained model
- This project is about Projection 3D point cloud (matching Camera Frame) using NumPy
- This project is in my Github repository: **3D-Object-Detection\_to\_2D\_Projection [Link]**

## **Basic Autonomous driving software**

Baram(Robotics Academic Group)

August.2021 - November.2021

May.2021 - August.2021

C++, ROS, DEEPLEARNING

- I trained Yolov3 model for Object detection
- It was implemented to make real-time judgment by using Yolov3 through ROS
- This project is in my Github repository: Basic\_Autonomous-Driving-Software [Link]

Console game Individual

I implemented a console game that avoids falling objects.

This project is in my Github repository: Console\_game-avoid\_object [Link]

SEPTEMBER 10, 2023

Sanghyun Park · Curriculum Vitae